Hello and welcome.
So from our previous videos we have done all the basic image processing.
Now in this video I will try to find the exact lead positions so far on my program.
These are my lead lines.
And in this video I will try to find the exact position of these lines with respect to the left side
of this frame.
So let's close this.
Now let us suppose this is over a frame and in this frame we have to lay lines let's say these are our
lean lines.
Now we have a frames and we have two lean lines.
Next I have to find a position off over a first line with respect to the left side of your frame.
Let's say that this distance will be a.
And we also have to find the position of this line with respect to the left side of your frame.
So let's say this distance will be be in our image processing.
We have to find the value of A and B at this time we also know our framework is fought under.
We updated a little framework.
And our frame height is 240.
Now the next question is how we can find these distances.
How we can find the value of A and B.
So to find the value of A and B I will again create a reason of interest.
So I will create a reason often best at the bottom and the size of this reason.
Interest really depends upon your choice.
So I have tried many reason of interest in this project but I find the best possible size is this.
So I will create a reason of interest of this size.
So let's say the word.
We know the words of although reason enough interest will be 400 and this hired will be a hundred and
the next question is how we can implement this reason of interest.
In other C++ language so we can implement this reason of interest by a rectangular command.
So for of rectangular more we need two points.
So our first plant will be this one.
And our second point will be this one.
So basically these are two gardeners and with these two gardeners we can draw a rectangle in our open
TV.
So let's say the coordinate of our first plant will be 0 0 mile 1 40
because of our frame height is 240 and a word of this reason often plus is hundred.
So the cardinal of this plant will be 0 or more 140 and Cardinals for this plant will be 400 which is
our frame word and frame height is our 240 here.
So the cardinals will be 400 comma 240 here.
Now I will use a rectangular command to read this of is enough interest in open TV so the syntax is
this rectangular.
Now for this event Look Ma we have four different parameters.
First is x.
Second is y told will be X plus a and fourth will be white plus B.
Now let's fill these values.
So rectangular.
Now what X and Y.
So the X and Y will be our first point.
So the first point is zero.
Come 140.
Now let us discuss both what are a and b.
So Ian B.
Nada.
These values of A will be the worth of this reason often trust and b will be the height of this reason
often trust.
So worth of reason often trust is 400 so 400 plus 0 will be 400
next why.
We know why is 140 and B is this hundred so we can see this value will be 240.
Now if I execute this command in our open TV then I will get this rectangle.
Now in the next half we have to process this rectangle in order to find the exact position of these
lead lines.
Now in open TV we cannot process this whole reason of interest at once.
So we have to divide this reason of interest into different strips.
So let's say I will divide this reason of interest into different strips
already so I divided my whole reason of interest into different strips and the worth of these tips will
be one pixel so same for all the shapes the worth of all the strips will be one pixel and height be
no height we have hundred pixels so the height is hundred pixels at this one if we get weird how many
pixels are in months.
So we can easily calculated so this will be hundred into one.
So in one step there will be total one hundred pixels and each pixels has an intensity of zero because
each pixel is dark so we can multiply with the needle and we will get the resultant intensity of the
zero and we will store this intensity in dynamic edit here.
So let's say our first element is zero because the intensity of one of our first trip is zero.
In the next step I will try to calculate the intensity for our next trip.
So next trip we have hundred pixel and each pixels have intensity zeros or hundred multiplied by zero
will be zero.
Same for our third strip.
Same for our fourth strip.
Now if I will get rid of the intensity for my fifth this trip then begin see we have total one hundred
pixels and each pixels had the intensity of 255 because each pixels are in white color.
We can multiply one hundred with their 255 and we will get some values.
So let's say this value is X and we will fill this value in this edit here X again.
If we try to process our next move so we will get zero again zero zero.
Then we will try to process this it will again get the value let's say x and gain for next trip X and
for all of the steps the value will be zero.
I also mentioned earlier the worth of each strip is one pixel.
So we need total 400 pixels in order to process our whole reason of interest.
So this will be over Eddie and in this added there will be total 400 elements and all these elements
will correspond to the intensity of each step for a reason of interest.
So this is the basic strategy that I will use to calculate the position of these chips.
Now this whole process is somehow related to the histogram process so we can also say we are calculating
it has to go for this image to calculate the position of these two lines.
Now let us implement the same thing in our C++ so let's go back to our project.