Hello and welcome.
At this point we are done with our calibration and this is the output from our previous video of a Lin
center is perfectly overlapping with all frames into now onwards.
We will start working on how we can steal our car between the lanes for this task.
We will need a variable that will tell us how much we are all set from our frame center.
All we can see how much is the difference between a lean centered and frame centered is for this task.
I will define a new variable here.
I will define the integer redeemable.
So let's say my variable name will be reserved and I will take a difference between Lane center and
frame center.
So Lane center minus frame center
next I have to declare this globally.
So I will declare it here.
So this is my result variable.
So in the next step I have to show this is old function on my original stream here on this frame.
I was sure this reserved for this task.
I will use the string stream.
So let us declare is string stream small string stream.
The name of the string stream will be let's say.
So this is the functionality of C++ but if you do not know about Springsteen seem you can easily learn
from Google.
Next will be your void main function.
So in the y loop I will define in detail to my string stream.
So let us first initialize this SS da SDR initialized with this space.
Next I will clear my previous string stream.
Next I will type that data to this string stream so data will be there say first I want to print the
desired
next every time the variable so desert variable.
Next I will use the opposite in functionality to print any text on the image so I will used up for text.
First parameter is what image so I just want a print on the frame.
Next I have to define my strings or SS da SDR for the data.
Next I have to define the point where I want to print the name.
So point to F.
So let's say one column of 50.
This will be the position next to parameters are the default which will describe the text type and text
scaling.
So I will type 0 column or 1 or default parameters.
Next will be of a color.
So scalar let's say I just want to print in the red color 0 0 0 0 0 mark 255
and last is a word bit of their text so let's say 2 pixels next compiler program.
All right so we have a edit I think again I made a silly text mistake.
Yes it is here.
So it is a string stream.
Next build it again.
All right so compilation is successful.
Let's run the program.
We can see the Z on the frame right now.
Our frame center is totally overlapping with a our line center.
That's why we are seeing a difference of zero.
Now let's do some experimentation with our self-driving car.
Let's move this to the left hand side.
That's perfect.
What is that video will have some positive value because we have offset between our lane center and
a low frame center which we can see from our final frame image.
Now let's try to move this Jesse to the other side.
All right now over a third variable goes negative.
Now move to the center and let's go back to our programming.
Alright so from this a variable I will steal my car between the lanes we have seen.
If I move my car into the left hand side then my Z video will goes positive.
But with some value in the same way if I move my car to the right hand side then this and variable goes
negative with some magnitude really so positive and negative saying shows that direction of movement
and magnitude are we can see the value defined the amount of movement to the particular direction.
So now onwards.
Bit of a result variable I will send the instruction to obviously device that is over Arduino you know
for communication.
I will try to connect the is helpings of raspberry pi to the Arduino you know to establish a communication
link but you can also use this severe communication if you want.
So far this project I believe is the parallel communication with the digital bins.
So in the next video we will see the process how we will connect a Raspberry Pi to our R2 we know you
know.